<FS19_StoryModeStory>
    <storyPartsCount>5</storyPartsCount>
    <storyParts>
        <story_1>
            <titleText>Introductions</titleText>
            <storyText>Hello there buddy. My name is Thomas Witherfield and I am the mayor of Felsbrunn! I heard you are interested in starting a farm here. Here is the deal: I offer you a starter loan and in exchange you are going to follow my plans. See, i have a vision in my mind of how we can make Felsbrunn so much more attractive to tourists and turn the fields around here into a beautiful scenery of growing plants of all variety and animals living in free range. Do you accept?</storyText>
            <storyOptions>1</storyOptions>
            <triggers_1>
                <triggerCount>0</triggerCount>
            </triggers_1>
            <bonus_1>
                <money>500000</money>
            </bonus_1>
            <nextStoryPart_1>2</nextStoryPart_1>
        </story_1>
        <story_2>
            <titleText>Buy your first patch of land</titleText>
            <storyText>Hello there buddy. I am glad you accepted my proposal. So let's get started, we have so much work ahead of us. Felsbrunn will become the greatest town. I am so glad I finally found someone willing to put in all the work. Let us start of by buying a patch of land to build you a farmhouse on. I would suggest field number 20, it has a lot of space for buildings and is not to expensive.</storyText>
            <storyOptions>1</storyOptions>
            <triggers_1>
                <triggerCount>2</triggerCount>
                <trigger_1 triggerType="fieldOwned"     triggerSticks="false" triggerAttributes="farmLandID:29" />
                <trigger_2 triggerType="propertyOwned"  triggerSticks="false" triggerAttributes="propertyName:FarmhousePlaceable" />
            </triggers_1>
            <bonus_1>
                <money>200000</money>
            </bonus_1>
            <nextStoryPart_1>3</nextStoryPart_1>
        </story_2>
        <story_3>
            <titleText>How about some machinery</titleText>
            <storyText>Now that you own the field and have a place to rest for the night, I think you should have a look around at the shop and invest in your first machinery. For starters you should buy at least one tractor, a plough or a grubber, and a sowing machine. With this equipment you can start taking care of the new field. Once you are done with this, we can start looking for tools to fertilize and take care of your crop and land. Also we will deal with getting you ready for the harvest later on. For now just buy everything you need for sowing first.</storyText>
            <storyOptions>1</storyOptions>
            <triggers_1>
                <triggerCount>3</triggerCount>
                <trigger_1 triggerType="machineryOwned"  triggerSticks="false" triggerAttributes="vehicleType:tractor-1" />
                <trigger_2 triggerType="machineryOwned"  triggerSticks="false" triggerAttributes="vehicleType:sowingMachine-1" />
                <trigger_3 triggerType="machineryOwned"  triggerSticks="false" triggerAttributes="vehicleType:plough-1" />
            </triggers_1>
            <bonus_1>
                <money>0</money>
            </bonus_1>
            <nextStoryPart_1>4</nextStoryPart_1>
        </story_3>
        <story_4>
            <titleText>Plough and sow</titleText>
            <storyText>We will talk again when you are done ploughing and sowing the field. Just pick any grain you like, so you can later use a standard harvester. I have some other business to attend to, see you later</storyText>
            <storyOptions>1</storyOptions>
            <triggers_1>
                <triggerCount>2</triggerCount>
                <trigger_1 triggerType="statToCheck"  triggerSticks="false" triggerAttributes="statToCheck:ploughed-100" />
                <trigger_2 triggerType="statToCheck"  triggerSticks="false" triggerAttributes="statToCheck:sown-100" />
            </triggers_1>
            <bonus_1>
                <money>20000</money>
            </bonus_1>
            <nextStoryPart_1>5</nextStoryPart_1>
        </story_4>
        <story_5>
            <titleText>Fertilize</titleText>
            <storyText>Now that you have sown the field. Go back to the shop and buy yourself something to fertilize the field and don't forget to get something against the growing weed. This could really diminish your harvest otherwise</storyText>
            <storyOptions>1</storyOptions>
            <triggers_1>
                <triggerCount>1</triggerCount>
                <trigger_1 triggerType="statToCheck"  triggerSticks="false" triggerAttributes="statToCheck:fertilized-100" />
            </triggers_1>
            <bonus_1>
                <money>20000</money>
            </bonus_1>
            <nextStoryPart_1>5</nextStoryPart_1>
        </story_5>
    </storyParts>
</FS19_StoryModeStory>